The Wolfpack Is Back
The Hangover Part II is a comedy film directed by Todd Phillips.
The Hangover crew heads to Thailand for Stu's wedding.
After the disaster of a bachelor party in Las Vegas last year, Stu
is playing it safe with a mellow pre-wedding brunch.
However, nothing goes as planned and Bangkok is the perfect
setting for another adventure with the rowdy group.
Phil Wenneck, played by Bradley Cooper.
Stu Price, played by Ed Helms.
Alan Garner, played by Zach Galifianakis.
Doug Billings, played by Justin Bartha.
Teddy, played by Mason Lee.
Mr. Chow, played by Ken Jeong.
The Hangover Part II is a 2011 American comedy film and sequel to the 2009 film
The Hangover, and the second installment in The Hangover trilogy.
The film was directed by Todd Phillips, who co-wrote the script with Craig Mazin and Scot Armstrong, and stars
Bradley Cooper, Ed Helms, Zach Galifianakis, Ken Jeong, Jeffrey Tambor, Justin Bartha, and Paul Giamatti.
It tells the story of Phil, Stu, Alan, and Doug, as they travel to Thailand.
After the bachelor party in Las Vegas, Stu takes no chances and
opts for a safe, subdued pre-wedding brunch.
Things do not go as planned, resulting in another bad
hangover with no memories of the previous night.
Development began in April 2009, two months before The Hangover was released.
The principal actors were cast in March 2010 to
reprise their roles from the first film.
Production began in October 2010, in Ontario, California,
before moving on location in Thailand.
Produced by Legendary Pictures, Green Hat Films and
BenderSpink, and distributed by Warner Bros.
Pictures, the film premiered at the TCL Chinese Theatre on May 19,
2011 and was released theatrically on May 26, 2011.
It became the eighth-highest-grossing film of 2011 and the highest-grossing
R-rated comedy during its theatrical run, and received mixed reviews.
A third installment, The Hangover Part III, was released on May 24, 2013.
The film explores themes of stag night, memory loss, undercover cop, drugs.
The tone is lighthearted.